Papa, the show is at 5:00.
I will be late.  Hey friend, you can make something
light.  Wait, I will call mom and
ask her when she will come.  Hello mom, when will
you come home?   It will take
me about an hour.
Look, his call also came.  Make something quickly.
[Music]
Yes, turn left from the park.
Half the movie will be over.
[Music]
And what are you doing these days, son?  Uncle has just
completed 12th.  Just what have you thought about the
future?  He is
very fond of acting etc.
Hello uncle.   Please
tell me a good college for acting.
Brother, if you want to go into acting
then take admission in LPU.
Well, does they teach acting etc. there
also?
Yes, there are many courses there like
Theatre and Music, Performing Arts.
But son, where is so much scope in this line
?
Uncle, he has connections with big companies.
Like Star Bharat, Colors, Zeev, if the
son studies there then where will he
get time for acting?  Uncle LPO has
launched the ED revolution.  Where students can
decide the curriculum as per their convenience.
Papa, I have also heard a lot about LPO.
Yes brother, it comes at fourth position in the world university ranking.
Okay, I will
go there once again and find out.